



Nguyen Ngoc Hiep

- **30/05/1998**
- **4** 0968958647
- ♥ Tan Lap, Dan Phuong, Ha Noi, Vietnam
- Male
- □ ngochiep30051998@gmail.com
- LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/hiệp-nguyễn-b89 aa1189

SUMMARY

I am a Software Engineer with about 5 years of experience in Web Development. I have 5 years of experience in Modern Front-End Web Development, 2 years in Mobile Cross-Platform Development and over 2 years in Nodejs related technologies.

With my knowledge, I enjoy solving front-end problems and creating the best user experience for users. I also spend time learning new technologies and best practices to become a better engineer.

WORK EXPERIENCE

WEB APPLICATION DEVELOPER

Jul 2020 - Present

VNPAY

Main responsibilities:

- Web application developer
- · Front-end team leader

Technology:

- · Back-end: Nodejs/ Nestjs
- Front-end: Angular 8+/ Ionic 7 / Reactjs/ Next.js
- · Database: PostgreSQL/ MySQL
- Other: CI/CD/ Docker/ NGINX/K8S

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

May 2020 - Present

FREELANCE

Main responsibilities:

Mobile/Web application developer

Technology:

- · Back-end: Nodejs/ Expressjs/Nestjs
- Front-end: Angular2+/Ionic 4+/Reactis
- Database: MongoDB
- · Other: OAuth/ Stripe

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

May 2020 - Jul 2020

LISOD

Main responsibilities:

Mobile/Web application developer

Technology:

- · Back-end: NodeJS
- Front-end: Angular 5+ / Ionic 4+ / Reactjs
- Database: MySQL/ Firebase
- · Other: Docker/ NGINX

WEB APPLICATION DEVELOPER

Jul 2018 - May 2020

POWERGATE SOFTWARE

Main responsibilities:

Mobile/Web application developer

Technology:

- · Back-end: NodeJS/ PHP/ Laravel
- Front-end: Angular 5+ / Ionic 4+

Database: MySQL

PROJECT

VNPAY.VN

Mar 2021 - Present

VNPAY

Description:

- Website introduces VNPAY company and the services provided by this company
- Migrate website from Nuxt.js to Next.js

Role: Team leader

Members: 2 Back-end Developers, 4 Front-end Developers

Responsibilities:

- Define the architecture, coding convention
- Design the database schema, implement back-end services
- Migrate Front-end project from Nuxt.js to Next.js
- · Setup Docker, CI/CD, k8s for project

Technology:

- · Back-end: Nest.js
- Front-end: Next.js, Angular 14 (Admin site)
- · Database: PostgreSql
- Docker/K8s

Link: https://vnpay.vn

VNPAY CA VN

Jan/2023 - Present

VNPAY

Description:

Admin site. Portal site for the VNPAY CA

Role: Front-end Leader

Members: 4 Front-end Developers

Responsibilities:

- Coding, reviewing code & mentoring Junior member of the team to ensure code quality
- Implement important sections of the front-end application
- Define the architecture, coding convention, setup Docker, CI/CD, k8s for project
- Communicate with other team(Back-end, Business Analyst, Product Owner, Tester) on generating product roadmap

Technology:

- Angular 14 (Admin site)
- Next.js (Portal site)
- Docker/k8s

Link:https://vnpayca.vn

VNPAY INVOICE

Nov/2022 - Present

VNPAY

Description:

- Website VNPAY e-Invoice using nx workspace
- · Admin site, Portal site, Web SDK for the VNPAY e-Invoice

Role: Front-end Leader

Members: 8 Front-end Developers

Responsibilities:

- Coding, reviewing code & mentoring Junior member of the team to ensure code quality
- Implement important sections of the front-end application
- Define the architecture, coding convention, setup Docker, CI/CD, k8s for project
- Communicate with other team(Back-end, Business Analyst, Product Owner, Tester) on generating product roadmap

Technology:

- Angular 15 (Admin site, Portal site, Customer site)
- Ionic 7 (Web SDK)
- Docker/k8s

Link:

https://vnpayinvoice.vn

https://portal.vnpayinvoice.vn

VNPAY E-CONTRACT

Jun/2022 - Jun/2023

VNPAY

Description:

 Website VNPAY e-Contract using Micro Front-end structure and nx workspace

Role: Front-end Leader

Members: 4 Front-end Developers

Responsibilities:

- Coding, reviewing code & mentoring Junior member of the team to ensure code quality
- · Implement important sections of the front-end application
- Define the architecture, coding convention, setup Docker, CI/CD, k8s for project
- Communicate with other team(Back-end, Business Analyst, Product Owner, Tester) on generating product roadmap

Technology:

- Angular 15
- Docker/k8s

Link: https://vnpaycontract.vn/app/auth

VNPAY T-VAN

Feb/2022 - Present

VNPAY

Description:

- · Admin site for the VNPAY T-VAN
- Portal site

Role: Front-end Leader

Members: 3 Front-end Developers

Responsibilities:

- Coding, reviewing code & mentoring Junior member of the team to ensure code quality
- Implement important sections of the front-end application
- Define the architecture, coding convention, setup Nginx + CI/CD for project
- Communicate with other team(Back-end, Business Analyst, Product Owner, Tester) on generating product roadmap

Technology:

- Angular 13 (Admin site)
- Reactis (Portal site)

Link: https://tvan.vnpay.vn/

YEAR-END CONCLUSION MODULE

Nov/2021 - Dec/2021

VNPAY

Description:

· Webview for the year-end summary module of VNPAY e-wallet

Technology:

Reactis

Role: Front-end Developer

Member: 1

INTERNET BANKING EXIMBANK OMNI CHANEL

May 2021 - Present

VNPAY

Description:

Allows a user to conduct financial transactions via the Web platform

Role: Web Front-end Developer

Members: 3 Web Front-end Developers

Responsibilities:

- Coding, reviewing code & mentoring Junior member of the team to ensure code quality
- Implement important sections of the fron-tend application
- Define the architecture, coding convention, setup Nginx + CI/CD for project
- Communicate with other team(Designer, Back-end, Backoffice, mobile, Business Analyst, Product Owner, Tester) on generating product roadmap

Technology:

• Angular 11

Link: https://edigi.eximbank.com.vn

INTERNET BANKING BIDV OMNI CHANEL

Jul 2020 - Present

VNPAY

Description:

Allows a user to conduct financial transactions via the Web platform

Role: Web Front-end Developer

Members: 3 Web Front-end Developers

Responsibilities:

- Coding, reviewing code & mentoring Junior member of the team to ensure code quality
- Implement important sections of the front-end application
- Define the architecture, coding convention, setup Nginx + CI/CD for project
- Communicate with other team(Designer, Back-end, Backoffice, mobile, Business Analyst, Product Owner, Tester) on generating product roadmap

Technology:

Angular 8

Link: https://smartbanking.bidv.com.vn

EDEYANS

May 2020 - Jul 2020

LISOD

Description:

 Create a management page (admin site) for the application to search and manage the cleaning of homes, offices, hotels ...

Technology:

Angular 6

Role: Front-end developer

Members: 2

YSLIFE

May 2020 - Jul 2020

LISOD

Description:

- Create realtime chat module integrated into react native webview section using firebase realtime database
- The project creates 2 mobile apps for gyms and coaches
- Coaches can create classes, add members to switch join to workouts, schedule assignments, and tailor-made diets.

Members: 4 Technology:

- · Web front-end: Reactis
- · Mobile front-end: React native
- Back-end: Expressis
- Front-end chat module: Ionic 4
- · Back-end chat module: Firebase

• Database: MySql / Firebase realtime database

Role: Full Stack developer

Members: 4

YMACAU

ILOSE

Jul 2018 - Feb 2019

Feb 2019 - May 2020

POWERGATE SOFTWARE

Description:

This is a white-label app project. Users can develop an application using available components in the system (layout, interface, data, ...) by the web platform. The highlight of the application is that it displays a preview, helping users to visualize the application before release. It also helps users to update their apps without having to release a new build.

Technology:

• Web front-end: Angular 7

• Web back-end: Expressjs

• Mobile front-end: Ionic 4

· Mobile back-end: Laravel

Database: MySql

Role: Full Stack developer

Members: 4

POWERGATE SOFTWARE

Description:

 The ILose weight loss tracker (can be found on the CH play or app store), mentors provide mentors with body metrics so that mentors can track and come up with the right solutions each section.

Technology:

Web front-end: Angular 5
Mobile front-end: Ionic 3
Role: Front-end developer

Member: 3

EDUCATION

MAJOR: INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY

Sep 2016 - Dec 2020

MILITARY TECHNICAL ACADEMY

GPA: 2.96/4

CERTIFICATIONS

TOEIC 525 2018

International Academy of Information Technology Training NIIT - ICT Hanoi Short-term PHP course 2018

Bachelor of Information Technology Military Technical Academy 2020

Enhancing Management Capacity for Middle Manager 2023